commentsbar.com 2015-02-04

# Privacy Policy

    **_Notice to Search Protect Users._**  
     Search Protect is provisionally certified as a Trusted Download Program by TRUSTe signifying that Search Protect has been tested by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe's TDP program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding Search Protect, please contact us at ClientConnect Ltd. Azrieli Center 1, Building A, 4th Floor 26 HaRokmim St. Holon 5885849, Israel or by email at support@trovi.com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe [here.](http://clicktoverify.truste.com/pvr.php?page=validate&softwareProgramId=498&sealid=112)   
    
    THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT EXPLAINS THE INFORMATION, COLLECTION AND USE POLICIES OF CLIENTCONNECT LTD. D/B/A TROVI AND ANY OF ITS AFFILIATED COMPANIES ("TROVI", “WE” or “US”) WITH RESPECT TO THE WEBSITES, SERVICES, PRODUCTS, TECHNOLOGY, SOFTWARE AND/OR SOFTWARE COMPONENTS (COLLECTIVELY, THE "SOFTWARE & SERVICES") OF TROVI THAT YOU INSTALL, USE, ACCESS OR INTERACT WITH ("USE"), BUT EXCLUDES SOFTWARE AND/OR SERVICES THAT HAVE SEPARATE PRIVACY POLICIES THAT DO NOT INCORPORATE THIS PRIVACY POLICY. BY INSTALLING, USING, ACCESSING AND INTERACTING WITH THE SOFTWARE & SERVICES, YOU CONSENT TO THE DATA PRACTICES AND INFORMATION COLLECTION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS STATEMENT. TROVI IS COMMITTED TO PRESERVING THE PRIVACY OF ITS USERS. THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT EXPLAINS WHAT INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT AND HOW WE MAY USE IT.  
    IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH HEREIN, DO NOT USE THE SOFTWARE & SERVICES.   
    
    YOU CONSENT TO THE DATA PRACTICES AND INFORMATION COLLECTION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS STATEMENT. TROVI IS COMMITTED TO PRESERVING THE PRIVACY OF ITS USERS. THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT EXPLAINS WHAT INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT AND HOW WE MAY USE IT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH HEREIN, DO NOT USE THE SOFTWARE & SERVICES.
    
    This Privacy Policy explains how Trovi treats your information and protects your privacy when you Use the Software & Services and the rights and options available to you regarding your information. Trovi believes that you have a right to know our practices regarding the information we may collect and use when you Use the Software & Services. The Software & Services may include various features and content that are offered and delivered to you by us and/or by third parties, such as news, messages, advertisements and games, as well as features and content that you may choose to add (“Content”).
    
     **The issues covered under this Privacy Policy:**
    
      *  Information Trovi Collects and Receives;
      * How Trovi Uses Your Information;
      * Sharing Information with Third Parties;
      * Third-Party Content;
      * Social Networks;
      * Cookies and Other Technologies;
      * Children under 13;
      * Access;
      * Data Retention;
      * Transfer of Data Outside Your Territory;
      * Information Security;
      * Do Not Track;
      * Changes to This Privacy Policy;
      * How to Contact Trovi.

    **_Information Trovi Collects and Receives._**
    
     When you Use the Software & Services, we automatically collect and store the following types of information:

      1. __Technical Information.__ Certain technical information regarding your device, and your Use of the Software & Services and other third party software and applications installed on your device (the **“Other Software”** ), including the type, name and version of the operating system and Other Software including, without limitation, their interactions with the Software & Services, ISP (Internet Service Provider), location, Internet protocol (IP) address, anonymous user identifiers, device configuration and identifiers (IDFA (Identifier for Advertisers used in IOS), Advertising ID (Identifier for Advertisers used in Android) and  the like), version of the Software & Services, and your configuration and settings of the Software & Services;

      2. __Usage Information.__ Certain usage related information regarding your use and interaction with your device, including the Software & Services and Other Software, such as when and how you Use the Software & Services and Other Software, how you use your internet browser and internet search related applications, the web pages you visit and the content you see, access and utilize on such web pages; for example, offerings and advertisements that you view, use and access, how you use them and your response to them, how frequently you use them, your search queries and the time and date of your searches;

      3. __Social Networks.__ Your interactions on social networks through the Software & Services;

      4. __Registration Related Information.__ Information you provide when you register for the Software & Services (if applicable), such as name, home or work addresses, email address, telephone and fax numbers, birth date and gender; and

      5. __Support Related Information.__ If you communicate with us via our support section or via email, we may also collect your email address, name and any information voluntarily submitted by you in connection with such support (for example, your name, company name, and particular support query or request). Such information will only be used to provide you with support services and will not be connected with any other information collected from you on or through the Software & Services, including, any individual User ID (as defined below) generated or collected by us.

                        When you Use the Software & Services, we automatically generate an anonymous internal user ID (which does not personally identify you), which is assigned to your use of the Software & Services (the **"User ID"** ) and may be combined with any of the above information.

                        While it is not our intention to collect any personally identifiable information (“ **PII** ”) (except for registration and user support purposes as set forth in this Privacy Policy), the data collected may include PII. As part of our privacy measures, we implement certain rules designed to avoid the unintentional collection of PII such as email addresses, social security numbers, credit card numbers, login information, etc. Such rules are based on known field types, parameters, values and algorithms but they are not foolproof and hence the Software & Services may sometimes, unintentionally, collect unwanted information. We regularly examine and update these rules.   
    
    **_How Trovi Uses Your Information._**
    
     Trovi uses the information it collects for analytical, business and operational purposes in the following ways:

      1. to operate and update the Software & Services and provide you with existing and new functionality and features;

      2. to improve and customize the Software & Services;

      3. to provide you personalized content, including through the delivery of targeted interest-based advertisements from us or our partners;

      4. to maintain and improve the quality and operation of the Software & Services;

      5. to notify you of Software & Services updates;

      6. to provide you with support and handle your complaints and/or feedback;

      7. to take any action in case of a dispute involving you in connection with the Software & Services;

      8. to enforce the terms and conditions applicable to the Software & Services and to prevent unlawful activities and misuse thereof; and

      9. to comply and satisfy any applicable law regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.

    **_Notice to Search Protect Users_**
    
     Search Protect is a free desktop application designed to help you maintain your selected browser settings, including your home page, default search and new tab, and prevent third parties from changing these settings without your permission.  Despite what is stated above, if you installed Search Protect, please note that the current version of the software does not track any of the web pages you visit or provide you with personalized content through the delivery of targeted, interest-based advertisements.   
    
    **_Sharing Information with Third Parties._**
    
     We may share with third parties the information collected in any of the following events:

      * If we are required by law to disclose your information, we may share your information with law enforcement or other competent authorities and any third party, as may be required (e.g., to detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; to respond to claims or satisfy any legal process, subpoena, or governmental request; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Trovi’s users, its partners, or the general public);

      * In the event Trovi goes through a business transition such as a merger or acquisition by another company, consolidation, change of control, reorganization, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your information will be among the assets transferred;

      * We may share your information with certain third parties (including, without limitation, search engines, content providers, and advertising networks and platforms) that provide various services (such as advertising, marketing, analysis, content, and search) in connection with the Software & Services. We take appropriate measures to ensure that no user can be individually identified from the disclosure of such information, and we require these third parties (i) to keep the data secured, (ii) not to use the data for any purpose other than to provide us with services, and (iii) to use the data solely in compliance with this Privacy Policy; and

      * We may also share PII and non-personally identifiable information with our subsidiaries, affiliated and parent companies, but their use of such information must comply with this Privacy Policy.

                        In any case other than the above, we will not share your PII with third parties without your prior consent.   
    
    **_Third-Party Content._**
    
     Certain Software & Services may include and/or enable you to add Content to them. The Content may be in the form of apps, buttons, gadgets, links to third-party advertisements, websites, products and services (including search services) as well as additional means that are provided to you by third parties (collectively, **"Third Party Content and Services"** ). The use of such Third Party Content and Services is subject to their privacy policies. In addition, Trovi provides such third parties with a large number of tools to enable them to create interesting and unique apps, buttons, and gadgets using the Trovi platform. Some of these tools may give these third parties the ability to access, collect, store, and/or share your information – both your PII and non-personally identifiable information. In order to clarify, we do not review, approve, monitor, endorse, warrant, or make any representations with respect to such Third-Party Content and Services and your access to any Third-Party Content and Services is at your own risk. We are not responsible for the information contained and/or made available through, the practices of, or your use or inability to use such Third-Party Content and Services. You expressly relieve us from any and all liability arising from your use of such Third-Party Content and Services. We recommended that you read the terms, conditions and privacy policies of such Third-Party Content and Services before using or accessing any of them.   
    
    **_Social Networks._**
    
     You may also choose to activate additional features that provide you with the ability to update and use your favorite social networks directly from the Software & Services. During such activation, you will be asked to grant Trovi permission to compile certain information from such social networks. This information may include friends or contact lists, notes, updates, and photos, and may be used by Trovi to customize the Content available to you through the Software & Services, suggest new features and Content that may be relevant to you, or provide Trovi with data for statistical purposes. The information you allow Trovi to access is that which is presented to you when you choose to activate these features. Please see your social network provider policies for any questions or concerns. You may opt not to grant Trovi access to your social network account(s) at any time by changing your social network settings or by not authorizing Trovi’s access thereto.   
    
    **_Cookies and Other Technologies._**
    
     We may collect or allow third parties to collect, through blocks of code called “pixels” or “web beacons”, certain information about you and send it to our servers and our partners. We or our partners package all or part of this information into small text files called Cookies and send the Cookie to your computer. For example, Cookies may store search queries made through the Software & Services, the web pages you accessed, your interaction with advertisements presented to you via the Software & Services, features you used, your session duration and your configurations and preferences of the Software & Services.
    
    Such Cookies and other technologies allow us and our partners to recognize you on your next use of, access or visit to the Software & Services, or on your visits or access to our partner’s network (i.e., sites and services outside of Trovi).
    
    Trovi and/or its partners use Cookies and other tracking technologies to:

      * facilitate and enhance your interaction and activities with the Software & Services;

      * help Trovi learn how you Use the Software & Services, what parts are most attractive and interesting to you, and what kind of offers you like to see;

      * provide you with personalized content which may include interest-based information, online ads or other marketing materials on or through the Software & Services and on third party websites and properties;

      * analyze the information collected from you and help manage and optimize the Software & Services;

      * track and measure various performance and demographic parameters of advertising campaigns including, without limitation, analyzing which ads your browser has loaded, which site pages you may have been viewing when the ads were delivered or accessed, and your interaction with the ad.

                        Most browsers are initially set up to accept Cookies but you can reset your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate when a Cookie is sent. However, some functions of the Software & Services may not function properly if your Cookies are disabled. By using the Software & Services, you affirmatively consent to the collection of information and Cookies as described above.   
    
    **_Children under 13._**
    
     The Software & Services are not intended for users under the age of 13 and you hereby represent that you are at least 13 years old. We do not knowingly collect, use, share or disclose any personal information from children under the age of 13. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage, so that we can verify that minors under the age of 13 are not using the Software & Services.
    
    We advise parents and guardians to regularly monitor their children's use of email and other online communications and activities. Control tools that create a safer online environment for children are available from third-party online services and software providers.
    
    In the event that it comes to our knowledge that a person under the age of 13 is using the Trovi Software, we will prohibit and block such a user from accessing the Software & Services, and will make all efforts to promptly delete any PII with regard to such user, as applicable.
    
    If you are a parent or guardian who has discovered that your child has submitted his or her PII without your consent, please contact us as provided in this Privacy Policy and we will take the necessary steps to remove that information from our database.  
    
    **_Access._**
    
     You may send us a request to access the PII that we collect through your use of the Software & Services. In such case, we may require that you provide us with additional information to verify your identity.   
    
    **_Data Retention._**
    
     We retain the information we collect as described in this Privacy Policy for as long as necessary to fulfill our business and/or operational purposes or comply with a legal request. We may also choose to anonymize parts of the information we collect so that it can no longer be identifiable or attributable to any person if we want to keep it for longer periods of time.   
    
    **_Transfer of Data Outside Your Territory._**
    
     The Software & Services work over the Internet. We may store and process information in various locations throughout the globe. If you are a resident of a European Union Member State or another jurisdiction where transfer of your PII to another jurisdiction requires your consent, then you hereby provide us with your express consent to such transfer of your data.     
    
    **_Information Security._**
    
     We implement measures to secure your PII that we collect in order to minimize the risks of damage, loss of information, and unauthorized access or use of information. However, these measures are unable to provide absolute information security. Therefore, although we make efforts to secure your PII, we cannot guarantee and you cannot reasonably expect that the Software & Services and its databases are immune from any wrongdoings, malfunctions, unauthorized interceptions, access, or other kinds of abuse and misuse.   
    
    **_Do Not Track._**
    
     Do Not Track is a privacy preference that can be configured in certain web browsers (the **"DNT Feature"** ); the DNT Feature, when enabled on a web browser, signals the websites you visit that you do not want certain information about the websites visited collected. As the Internet industry is in the process of defining how to interpret signals sent by the DNT Feature, Trovi does not currently respond or recognize DNT Feature signals.   
    
    **_Changes to This Privacy Policy._**
    
     We may, from time to time, change this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to visit and review this Policy frequently to stay informed. Prior to any material change to this Privacy Policy, Trovi will present you with a detailed notification (e.g., a pop-up notification or other reasonable means) of such change including information on how you may uninstall the Software & Services. Other changes, including amendments made to the Policy to comply with legal requirements, will become effective immediately upon their initial posting. Trovi will also update the "Last updated” date at the end of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Software & Services after any change takes effect will indicate your acceptance of the amended Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any of the amended terms, you must avoid any further use of the Software & Services.   
    
    **_How to Contact Trovi._**
    
     If you have any concerns or questions with respect to any matter covered by this Privacy Policy, you may contact us by email at: [privacy@trovi.com](mailto:privacy@trovi.com) or at the following address:
    
    ClientConnect Ltd.  
    26 HaRokmim Street, Azrieli Center 1  
    Building A, 4th Floor  
    Holon 5885849  
    Israel  
    Last updated: November 12, 2014
